vietnamtripadvisor.com 2014-12-28

# Privacy Policy

In order to inform you of how we use your data and what data we may collect; we have developed a privacy policy. We define personal information as any information that can be linked to you or used to identify you. This includes but isn’t limited to; your name, your address, your phone number, and your e-mail address.

### Your Personal Data – What We Collect, How We Collect It

If you ask us to make travel arrangements or to provide any other service to you; we will collect personal data from you this may include but is not limited to:

  * Name, mail address, phone number, e-mail, birth date, and student information
  * Your preferences for travel (class, seating, airlines, meals, etc.)
  * Any information necessary to facilitate any further services (passport number, visa number, emergency contacts, etc.)
  * Specific information necessary to resolve any issues or questions you may encounter
  * Information regarding payment this may include credit card details, billing address, etc.

If you enter one of our competitions or prize draws we may also collect personal information from you. We may also collect information in order to send you a brochure or other relevant material at your request. 

We try not to collect information from those under the age of 13. We believe that children are not capable of consenting to the use of their data and would ask those under the age of 13 not to provide us with any personal data whatsoever.

Our websites make use of “cookies”. These are small pieces of data which may help us analyze usage patterns on our sites and also to deliver a better browsing experience to our users. Your browser will almost certainly accept cookies by default but you are free to disable this by following your browser provider’s process for doing so. We do not store any identifiable information about our customers in the cookies we use.

We do not sell your data to any other company but we may make use of contact information provided to us to send out newsletters, offers, competitions, etc. We may occasionally use a monitoring tool to detect if emails we send out are opened by their recipients. This data is only used to help our marketing effectiveness and is not shared with anyone else.  
We also collect non-identifiable information whenever someone visits our sites. This may include the IP address of the visitor, their operating system, web browser, etc. 

### How do We Use the Information We Collect and Who Do We Share it With?

We use your information to fulfill the request we receive from you. This means that we may share information with hotels, airlines, car reservation companies, etc. in order to complete your booking. We only share the minimum amount of information necessary to comply with their processes. We work only with reputable suppliers but do not have any control over how they use your data within their own environments. 

We may also use your data for analysis within our own business and to fulfill any administrative or other tasks necessary to bill you, support you, etc. We may also use your data to tailor any marketing material we send to you so that it is of the highest level of relevance. 

We do not share your data with any other party except as laid out above. We do not sell your data to third parties for any purposes.

If we run a competition it is possible that the rules of that competition may require your data to be shared with another party. We strongly suggest you read the rules of any competition prior to entering it and sharing your data.

If we are required by law to disclose information about you we will do so if appropriately informed by relevant authorities to do so. We do not routinely disclose information to any authority that we are not legally required to.

### The Security of Your Data

We take all appropriate measures to secure any personally identifiable data. We make all reasonable efforts to ensure that your data is safe. However, you should not assume that data transmitted over the internet is 100% secure. We encrypt all highly-sensitive data and use firewalls, anti-virus, etc. to protect your data. We do not give any warranty to the security of your data during any transaction.

### Third Party Sites and Links

Occasionally we may offer a link to a 3rd party website for your information or for other services. Our privacy policy does not apply to these 3rd party sites and you should read their privacy policy before deciding whether to share your data with these sites or not. We accept no liability for your data outside of our own environment.

### Questions or Concerns

If you need to let us know that data we’re holding is incorrect or wish us to remove your data from our systems you should contact help@asiatouradvisor.com. If you have any questions regarding our use of your data you should contact us at the same address. We will attempt to respond to your queries etc. within 72 hours of the receipt of your e-mail.

### Other Information

This privacy policy was developed on the 28th of April, 2013. We may at our own discretion revise this policy at any time and those revisions are effective as soon as they are posted. You should be sure to check back here occasionally to ensure that you remain up to date with our approach. If we make any significant changes we will try to notify you via the e-mail address we have on file. If you use our websites after changes are posted, your use of the website constitutes acceptance of our new policy.
